[♪ opening theme song playing]
[both growling]
I suppose...
I'll give this one a try.
[both growling]
Way off! This'll take
some adjustment!
[thudding]
Gabby.
Are there any assailants
in your area?
[GABBY] Yeah,
something came at me.
When did these freaks
manage to get inside the manor?
Guess you're dealing
with some guys of your own?
[JIN] Yeah, we're dealing
with a pair as we speak.
[grunts]
[GABBY] Well,
take care of 'em already.
[JIN] I'm trying,
but with limited mobility.
Huh? Don't give me that crap!
Don't you have
Asa there with you?
You'd better protect her!
[JIN] We have Yuru
and his daemons.
They're helping.
[GABBY] Those guys
who knocked my teeth in?
[grunts] Dumb bastards.
You'll be fine then.
You mind if I just
do my thing over here?
[JIN] Be my guest.
Thank you.
[grunts]
Gobble.
[screeches]
[GABBY] What to do?
It would just be so cruel
to leave you
-alone without your other half.
-[whimpers]
Gobble.
[whimpers]
[Gabby smirks]
Aren't you lucky, Gabriel?
You get a midnight snack!
It seems Miss Gabby
is managing all right.
Thank goodness.
Now how about I stop them?
[YURU] You can do that?
[ASA] If I do, can I hug you?
You're so big
you'd break my ribs.
Hey, Jin. Sorry if I make
a mess of this place.
I'll take the heat
from the old man.
Do whatever you have to.
Hey, Jin, I'm also sorry
if I make a mess of this place!
[JIN] You're gonna have
to take the heat yourself.
[HARUO] What a blatant
double standard!
Give me a hand!
Brother, go ahead
and distract the white one!
Don't give me orders.
But I'm on it.
[both growling]
[Asa gasps]
[Yuru gasps]
Where'd she go?
Asa?
[JIN] She vanished.
And Yuru, too?
What is this thing?
Stop it!
[HARUO] I don't know
what they did,
but it seems like they make
people disappear.
So there's a chance
these guys are the ones
who kidnapped Asa's parents!
[JIN] The damage
to the floorboards is fine,
but no killing.
Them or their master.
[HARUO] Got it, boss man.
Haruo, there are enemy daemons
on all sides!
[HARUO] Uh?
I'm needed here!
It's all you, Jin!
[JIN] What?
[BUNBUN] Me too! Haruo needs
his bodyguard!
[JIN] Really?
[Jin groans]
Why's it gotta happen
when the master Natsuki
and Fuyuki are all out?
So, where's Hagure?
[SAKURAZAWA]
Sleeping after a tight deadline.
Wake him,
and it'll be your head.
[Jin sighs]
[JIN] No reinforcements then.
Well, my friends,
let's get to work.
Late night, long shift.
[ASA] Big Brother! Yuru!
[echoes]
Hey, Jin? Or Haruo?
Or Doctor Sakurazawa?
Hey, Ai?
Makoto?
Torty, maybe?
Or Bunbun?
[Asa sighs]
I'm all alone.
[Asa breathes shakily]
[Asa whimpers]
You're not as alone
as you think you are!
[Asa screams]
My brother's daemon?
[RIGHT] Yeah,
but you can call me Right.
It's too dark in here
to see you.
[RIGHT] I'm out of luck too.
But rest assured, I'm nearby.
You know,
this is serious darkness.
Even Higashi Village
in the dead of night
can't compare.
Can't see my own hand. Hm?
You reek
of cold sweat, lass.
Are you afraid of the dark?
♪
[ASA] Not always.
Just... when I'm alone.
[RIGHT] Your scent
is coming from this way.
Don't fret, lass.
I'm right by your side.
I'm not gonna leave you
to fend for yourself.
[Asa sighs softly]
[Asa yelps] Where's my brother?
Is Yuru here?
You would be able to tell
if he were, would you not?
Doesn't smell like
he's stuck in this place.
Aren't you contracted
to take care of him?
Why aren't you rushing
straight to his side?
He's got Left, so I can't say
I'm too concerned.
They'll figure something out.
I followed you because
I thought we should chat.
Or are you busy right now?
What do you want?
[RIGHT] You fired at me
when we first met.
A blast of energy
straight out of your hand.
And you haven't been much warmer
since I came to this manor.
You didn't see fit to offer me
a simple hello?
Or maybe you already realized
that I'm your enemy.
[Asa grunts softly]
[ASA] Back then,
when you countered...
Or... No... Maybe canceled?
What did I do?
[ASA] I'm sorry.
It's hard to describe.
Neutralized?
Yeah, when you
neutralized Break,
something my father said
came back to me.
He said Left and Right
are guardians.
They're to keep Break and Seal
from ever getting
out of control.
That makes this talk
easy for me!
As the wielder of Break,
you're my nemesis.
Nice to meet you, Asa.
[ASA] On the other hand,
if my brother acquires
the power of Seal,
she'll be his nemesis, too.
Such is the natural order
of things, I suppose.
[yelps] You're here too, Left?
Aye, in this void.
An odd place.
Yeah, just where are we?
No idea. I've lived
many a lifetime and more,
and yet this is still new.
How strange.
There is ground.
But all of this white
is distorting my perception.
While flying, I found... a roof?
Or something like?
It seems we are closed in.
I cannot be certain,
but it appears we're inside
a spherical barrier
made by the daemon pair
from before.
We're trapped in a barrier?
[Yuru grunts]
[YURU] Are there
any enemies around?
[LEFT] Far as I can tell,
there is naught else here
but us.
All right, then I would like
some help adjusting to this bow.
-You mind?
-Is now the right time?
I've got no clue
what's going on,
but I don't want
to just stand around.
My father taught me to keep
my tools in good condition.
And to be ready
for a fight anywhere
with whatever
I've got on hand.
Does being
in such an unfamiliar situation
hold no fear for you?
Why should I fear anymore?
It's been the same every day.
Nothing has made sense
since the village was attacked.
Why would I feel afraid
when being confused
has become so normal to me?
-[Yuru chuckles]
-[LEFT] Poor lad.
♪
[YURU] Stand there and raise
the billhook high.
That's my target.
[LEFT] Like this?
[YURU] Perfect.
Don't just let it hit you!
[LEFT]
Retrieving the arrows later
would be obnoxious
if I were to dodge them now.
[YURU] Yeah, but come on!
No reason to worry.
As I told you,
I'm sculpted of stone.
[YURU] I am so sorry!
Hey, are these on straight?
[LEFT] Are you not concerned
for your sister's well-being?
[YURU] Huh? What for?
[LEFT] As we are trapped here,
she was swallowed by
the black daemon's barrier.
Well, yeah. But she's got
that Break thing.
If they really are barriers,
I figure she'll be fine.
[both growling]
What, Torty?
[grunting]
[ASA] We're out!
Aye! So, the barrier
was inside this daemon!
-[Haruo exclaims]
-Glad you're back, Asa!
Thanks, Bunbun!
As for you...
I'm going to take your contract
with your master and Break it!
[grunting]
[SAKURAZAWA] Heads up.
Weren't you just telling Jin
how unsanitary carrying this is?
Sorry, it's not fresh.
[sizzling]
I'm your master now.
[grunts]
I'll be taking good care of you,
I promise.
[Asa grunts softly]
Aw! They're more friendly
than I expected!
[grunts] I wonder
what their names are.
I've got you.
Save a little for later.
We have time.
Though, why isn't
my brother here, too?
Did you see where he went
when I was trapped inside?
[grunts]
[Asa yelps] Spit him out!
Spit him out!
Let him go right now!
[HARUO] They're out.
[ASA] Are you okay?
[yelps] Slow down, there!
Those two are on our side now!
Explain it to me!
Uh, I used my Break power
to free those daemons
from their contract.
They're mine now!
They have the ability to make
people vanish into thin air!
Do you understand?
Their old master might know
something about your parents!
All we have to do now
is track them down.
Great. But how?
[ASA] I have another request.
I want to know where
your previous master's hiding.
Will you show me?
[grunts]
She's making a daemon pair
sell out their old master.
[SAKURAZAWA] Teenagers do get
scarier by the day, huh?
[Hamura gasps]
Oh, come on, that's cheating!
I can't believe
they gave me up so quickly.
What stupid daemons!
Over there? It's too dark for...
[grunting]
-[Hamura screams]
-Hey, Right, mind grabbin' him?
I'm on it!
[YURU] Good.
Anyone else out there?
[ASA] Holy crap.
He grew into
such a good hunter.
[cries]
I'm so proud of him!
What's wrong?
Apologies for all the noise.
As non-combatants,
please keep hidden.
We should have the situation
resolved shortly.
[BOTH] Right.
[ASSASSIN] Yeah.
Keep walkin', buddy.
We'll blow you sky high.
[screaming]
[grunting]
[laughter]
[assassin gasps]
Good. That wasn't too hard.
Yet another face
I haven't seen before.
Hey, nice job, Jinny!
I don't think any of these guys
were Kagemori.
The five pairs I've killed
have all been garbo.
Mine have also been "garbo."
For real?
[assassin screams, grunts]
[groaning]
[GABBY] Another fresh face.
[ASSASSIN]
No, no, no, no... [screams]
Don't kill me. Her dentures
already got my daemons!
I surrender!
Huh, who shot this?
I guess Yuru's back.
[GABBY]
I don't even see the lunatic.
[IVAN] Man, scary kid.
If I went out there,
I'd take one in the neck
before I ever got in range.
All our other guys have either
been captured or killed.
I think I'm gonna call it a day.
I'm not one for pain.
Should've known
this group of nobodies
wouldn't have
a snowball's chance.
So I'm outta here.
What a joke.
Only bothered takin' this job
'cause the pay's good.
Now I'm stuck having
to scrounge up new daemons.
[grunts]
[whimpers]
[gasps, grunts]
[thudding]
[bird cawing]
[birds chirping]
[HARUO] Nice work
taking out the trash, Jin.
[JIN] Yeah.
Awful lot of rodents this time.
You all right, kid?
Sorry for involving you.
You sure know
how to entertain your guests.
Thanks for the assist.
Don't get this twisted.
I am not on your side.
I only lent a hand
'cause it might help me
find my mom and dad.
Asa, you good?
[gasps]
-[GABBY] Huh?
-[Gabriel growls]
Stupid brat.
You little runt.
I may be small, but I bet you
I'm older than you.
[YURU] Liar!
[GABBY] Don't disrespect
your elders, son!
I let you walk away
with your life once.
Don't expect me to be so nice
if you cross me again.
Let's not start
another fight, guys.
Yuru and his guardians protected
this place by our side.
Yeah, no shit.
Just look at 'em.
He caught a crap ton.
-[Right roars]
-[both scream]
What should we do with 'em?
The master will decide
when he gets back to the manor.
It isn't for me to say.
Till then, let's ask them
some questions.
Talk to them, Haruo.
I'm on it.
[HAMURA] They offered me
a near fortune
if I could just capture
some twin kids.
Got no name or face
I could give you,
even if I were a snitch.
I think the old classic
should do the trick.
[HAMURA] Hm?
[HAMURA] Uh...
[grunts]
Why is it so damn heavy?
[screaming]
Who reached out to you
about this job?
Was it someone
from the Kagemori clan?
[screams] I swear to you,
I really don't know!
Please, stop it!
We're all just mercs!
I don't even know
any of the other people
I was workin' with! [gasps]
I'm tellin' you!
We're just some
dime-a-dozen daemon wielders!
Great, so you don't know
who hired you.
Surely you had someone
in charge on site?
The camo jacket.
He had a camo jacket
and a beard.
-He's in charge.
-[Akio gasps]
[Hamura grunts, yells]
[AKIO] I think
I dealt with that one.
I left him outside of the gate.
My bad.
[Hamura continues grunting]
Well, how about we move on?
We're looking
for a married couple
that fled Higashi.
What do you know?
They're these kids' parents.
They were
on their way to Okinawa
and vanished mid-flight.
No clue!
Now get this turtle off of me!
Think harder!
We'll take anything you know!
[HAMURA]
And I told you I got nothin'!
-I'm clueless too.
-Same here.
-Do you two know anything?
-[BOTH] Uh-uh.
[Yuru grunts softly]
Then after all this,
we're not any closer
to the truth.
I know how you feel.
Sorry your trip
was a waste of time.
[Yuru breathes shakily]
[Jin sighs]
Okay, last call.
Anyone else got a question?
[ASA] Yes.
Mind answering one for me?
[HAMURA]
If you get this thing off me!
Anything you want! Ask away!
What are the names you gave
our little friends here?
Their names? Huh? What?
What did you call them?
[HAMURA] Why bother
calling them anything?
If you're working with a daemon,
they deserve a name.
But they're like farm animals,
aren't they?
They're disobedient livestock,
so you gotta beat 'em
into shape
till they listen
to what you say.
Wouldn't name a mule
I used once. That's crazy.
[Gabriel growls]
Easy there, Gabs.
[GABBY] I'm gonna go change.
[YURU] Hm.
There it is.
Now I see why your daemons
turned on you without a thought.
You know, we've got feelings
of our own, mister.
[Hamura whimpers]
Got anything else to say?
Now's the time to cough it up.
-This was just some odd job!
-Same for me!
And let the record show
my daemons have names!
[BOTH] Uh-huh.
On that note, we can't
leave you without one.
So what to call you?
-[grunting softly]
-[laughs] Hey, cut it out!
I'm only your temporary master,
so don't get too attached to me!
You really are
quite affectionate.
[grunts] Do you have
a smaller form, by chance?
Oh, my gosh! You're so cute!
Weren't you saying earlier
how assassins have been
hounding you day after day?
Has your life been like that
since leaving the mountain?
Sort of.
But there were
so many this time around,
it seemed worse than usual.
And having you here to help
meant a lot.
Thank you.
[ASA] The manor's been
a safe haven for so long,
I stupidly let my guard down.
I'll be more careful.
[YURU]
If that's the way she thinks,
it's no wonder she's jaded.
-[YURU] Hey.
-[ASA] Uh?
[YURU] Your eye.
Did they take that
from you, too?
[ASA] Well,
I suppose in a way, yes.
[YURU] Hm?
[ASA] No, that's not right.
I don't want
any lies between us.
The truth is, I died once.
[YURU] Huh?
One of Higashi's assassins
killed me.
[Yuru breathes shakily]
[♪ closing theme song playing]
[YURU]
I could feel the hostility
through every pore on my body.
Under my skin,
stabbing straight through
my flesh and into my guts.